Wow!
(Raj:)And that's not even the best part.
(Raj:)See?
(Raj:)I have one, too.
(Raj:)Check it out.
(Raj:)You can wear yours,
(Raj:)and we can have little sword fights
whenever we want.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and my eighth favourite
episode of Professor Proton
was "Alka-Seltzer Rocket."
You said, "Plop, plop, fizz, fizz,
oh, what a blast-off it is."
(Sheldon:)Remember?
Remember that? Remember?
(Leonard:)He can't help it.
He can't. He really can't.
(Sheldon:)Wait here,
I'll get some Alka-Seltzer,
(Sheldon:)we can build that rocket,
(Sheldon:)and we can shoot it
at Bill Nye's house.
(Sheldon:)As long as I'm not
within 500 feet of it.
(Arthur:)So, you...
(Arthur:)You have... you have any...
(Arthur:)Single grandmothers?
(Penny:)Sorry, they're both married.
(Sheldon:)Good.
Ha--ha-
(Arthur:)happily?